Maybe you are interested in educating yourself as a criminologist?
Maybe you are interested in everything that has to do with crime?
Then maybe the criminal profession is something for you?
How can you train as a criminologist?
You can read at college and university.
You can read independent courses in criminology.
Criminology 1, 2 and 3 are often called the courses at different universities.
You can also read criminology programs.
A three -year program.
Leading to a philosophy bachelor's degree.
Here at Örebro University we have a criminology program
which is based on integrative modern criminology.
One may also practice very practical on how we can
Preventing crime and insecurity.
One is well prepared for a professional life that
I think it's reasonable that when you have a degree
from college or university in criminology
Then you can call yourself a criminologist.
If you wish.
Just as when you have read political science for three years at the university
and has a bachelor's degree.
Or behavioral science.
You probably hear people who call themselves political scientists and behavioral scientists.
Then maybe we can be called us criminologists when we read a bachelor's degree.
In criminology.
What can, but really work with as a criminologist?
You know a lot about crime and insecurity.
And security.
Almost all businesses are affected by it in different ways.
There are more examples of employers.
As you hear, there is a fairly proper labor market as criminologists.
What is the benefit of criminology?
You as a citizen and taxpayer:
What should you expect from us as a researcher in criminology?
Or a criminologist who has a bachelor's degree from us
And calls himself a criminologist?
I think you should high expectations of us who are scientific criminologists.
We should not just be thinkers and thinkers.
You should expect us to convey
Research to you and our decision makers.